A Guide to the William J. “Bill” Elvin Collection, 1914-2004, bulk 1963-2003
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 2: McLean Providence Journal Subject Files, 1925-2004
  - Clemyjontri Park, 2001-2003 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Clift, Eleanor, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Clinton, Bill and Hillary, 1998-2003 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Coleman, Beverly Mosby, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Coleman, John Marshall, 1981-1994 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Collier, Mary, Undated (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Collins, Theodore, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Colonial History, 1979-1994 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Colonies, The, Undated (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Colvin Run Mill, 1973-2003 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Colvin Run Road, Schoolhouse, Store, 1977-1999 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Commons, The, 1999-2002 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Community Council, Undated (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Concord Coalition, Undated (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Concorde (Airplane), 1976-2003 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Condominium Conversion, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Connolly, Gerry, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Control Data Corporation, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Cooke, Elizabeth Miles, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Corner Family, 1958-1997 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Cottonwood Street, 1986-1996 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Courts, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Covance Laboratories, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Cox Communications, 2000-2002 (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Cox, Archibald, Undated (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Crestar Bank, 1997-2000 (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Crime, 1974-1990 (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - Criminal Justice, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - D’Arcy, Diane, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - Danner, Pamela, 1994-1998 (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - Daoust, Lucy Frank, Undated (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - Daughters of the American Revolution, Undated (Box 16, Folder 78)
  - Davis, Gil, Undated (Box 16, Folder 79)
  - Davis, J.J. (J.J. Davis Associates), Undated (Box 16, Folder 80)
  - Davis, Tom, 1991-1999 (Box 16, Folder 81)
  - Day-Care, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 82)
  - Dear Family, 1992-1998 (Box 16, Folder 83)
  - DeBell, Stuart, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 84)
  - Deer Management, 1991-2002 (Box 16, Folder 85)
  - Defense Mapping Agency, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 86)
  - Democrats, Blue Dog, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 87)
  - Dewberry, Sidney, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 88)
  - DiBenedetto, T. and Anne, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 89)
  - Dick, Faith, Undated (Box 16, Folder 90)
  - Dickerson, Nancy, 1985-1997 (Box 16, Folder 91)
  - Disney’s America, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Dix, Robert B. Jr., 1993-1999 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Doctors - Fairfax County History, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Dogs Licenses, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Dolan, Bill, 1992-1998 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Dolan, Pat, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Dole, Elizabeth, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Dolley Madison Boulevard, 1987-2002 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Domenech, Daniel A., 1999-2003 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Dominican Retreat House, Undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Donaldson, Sam, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Donovan, John A.K., 1985-1993 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Doumar, George, Undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Dower House - Route 193, 1983-1993 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Downey, Morton Jr., 1971-2001 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Downey, Sean, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Doyle, Elly, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Drainsville - Miscellaneous, 1965-2001 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Drainsville Tavern, 1967-2001 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Drover’s Rest, Undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Dryden, Glenn, Undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - DuBois, Joan, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Dulles Access Road, 1978-1990 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Dulles Access Road, 1979-1991 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Dulles Airport, 1973-1995 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Dulles Corridor Rapid Transit, 1984-2002 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Dulles, Eleanor L., 1996 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Dunbar, Victor, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Dunkum, Ruby F., 2001 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Dunningham, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Durham, Jack and Ethel, 1991-1995 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - DuVal, Clive and Susan, 1990-2002 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - DWI/DUI, 1985-1988 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Dwoskin, Albert J., 1989 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Dyke, James W. Jr., 1992-1996 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Dykes, Frederick T., 1991-1995 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Dykes, Marcia, 1990-1992 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Dynalectron Corp., 1983 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Eakin, Ruth, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Eastern American Bank, 1992-1997 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Edgerton, Amy - Lewinsville Road, 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Edwards, Paul G., Undated (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Eight Oaks, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Elm Street, 1983-1992 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Elmwood, Undated (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Elvin, William J. - 1998 Calendar, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Elvin, William J. - Accomplishments, Correspondence, and Retirement, 1940-1992 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Elvin, William J. - Personal Notes, 1980-2001 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Elvin, William J. - Sources and Notes for History of Mclean, 1992-1997 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Elvin, William J. "Jim" (father), 1946-1958 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Emerson Gallery, Undated (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Emery, Mark, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Englat, William J., 1999 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Environment - Light Pollution, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Epstein, Sydney, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Espy, Ridgway, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Evans Farm Inn, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Everett, John, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Ewing, Charles B., Undated (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Fair Play for Fairfax, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Fairfax County Adult Detention Center, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Fairfax County Board of Supervisors, 1987-2000 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Fairfax County Board of Supervisors - Bribery, 1960-1997 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Fairfax County Courthouse, 1987-2002 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Fairfax County Drug Abuse, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Fairfax County Government Center, 1992-1995 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Fairfax County History, 1962-1991 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Fairfax County Housing, 1977-2001 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Fairfax County Park Authority, 1977-2003 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Fairfax County Parkway, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Fairfax County Schools, 1978-1992 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Fairfax County Schools - 1993 Budget, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Fairfax County Schools - Budget, 1964-2002 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Fairfax County Schools - Chapter 1 Programs, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Fairfax County Schools - Construction, 1960-1989 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Fairfax County Schools - Desegregation, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Fairfax County Schools - Drugs, 1986-1990 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Fairfax County Schools - Evaluation Programs, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Fairfax County Schools - Gifted and Talented Programs, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Fairfax County Schools - Outcome Accountability, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Fairfax County Schools - Parking, 1988-1991 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Fairfax County Schools - Population, 1963-1970 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Fairfax County Schools - Report Cards, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Fairfax County Schools - School Board, 1988-1997 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Fairfax County Schools - Sex Education, 1989-1991 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Fairfax County Schools - Superintendent Linton Deck Resignation, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Fairfax County Signs, Undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Fairfax County Solid Waste, 1983-1991 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Fairfax County Storm Drainage, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Fairfax County Taxes, 1988-1991 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Fairfax County Water, 1957-2000 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Fairfax Herald Newspaper, 1940-1999 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Fairfax Hospital, 1966-1988 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Fairfax Hunt, Undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Fairfax Station, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Fairfax, Bryan, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Fairfax, Lord, 1973-1986 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Fairies, Durward, 1998-2000 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Fairman, Delos "Dutch", 1998 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Falck, Nancy, 1983-1996 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Falls Church - Miscellaneous, 1988-1990 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Falls Church Water, 1975-2004 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Falls Reach, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Families, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Family Respite Center, 1985-1997 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Farm Credit Administration, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Farmers Market, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Farris, Michael, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Fay, Kevin, 2000-2003 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Federal Highway Administration - Francis C. Turner Building, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Federal Home Loan Mortgage Corporation, 1987-1991 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Feighery, Thelma, 1992-2001 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Fiber Optics, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Field, Joanne, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Finley, Stuart, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - First Baptist Church Chesterbrook, 1985-1996 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - First Union Bank, 1992-1998 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Fisher, Joseph L., Undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Fitzgerald, Robert, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Fitzpatrick, Joanna, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Flagg - Highland View, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Flannery, John, Undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Fleary, Dingwall, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Fletcher, Paul, Undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Flow General Inc., 1983 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Ford, President Gerald, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Ford’s Theater, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Foretich, Eric, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Fort Circle Parks, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Fort Marcy, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Foster, Bonnie, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Foster, Vince, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Fountains of McLean, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Four Mile Run, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Fox, Evelyn, 1997-1999 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Franklin Park, 1992-1997 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Franklin Sherman Elementary School, 1986-2000 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Franklin, Pat, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Freddie Mac, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Freeman, John Y., 1983 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Freeman, Robert M., 1998 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Freenet, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Freligh, Barbara, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Freligh, Steve, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Frey, John T., 1991 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Friedlander, Marc, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Frisbee, Lucy, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Frye, Bob, Undated (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Frying Pan Park, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Fuller, Craig, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Fuller, Stephen S., 2002 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Future Fairfax Foundation, Undated (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Gabriel, Col. Arnald, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Gallinek, Patricia, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Gannett Corporation, 1994-1999 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Garber, Thomas, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Garcia, Judy, 1986-1988 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Gartland, Joseph, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Gasch, Manning and Oliver, 1950-1999 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Gasper, Louis, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Gates of McLean, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Gehr, David R., 1984 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - General Assembly, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Gentry, Richard H., Undated (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - George Mason University [contains photograph], 1975-1997 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - George Washington Memorial Parkway, 1964-2000 (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - Georgelas Group [contains photographs], 1980-1991 (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Georgetown Pike, 1928-2000 (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Giant Food Stores, 1998-2002 (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Gibson, Lytton, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 74)
  - Gilmore, James, 1996-2002 (Box 19, Folder 75)
  - Gingrich, Newt, 1994-2000 (Box 19, Folder 76)
  - Glass Ceiling - Labor Issues, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 77)
  - Gold - Panning in Northern Virginia, 1975-1997 (Box 19, Folder 78)
  - Gold Cup, The Virginia, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 79)
  - Goralski, Margaret, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 80)
  - Gordy, Stephen E., 1982 (Box 19, Folder 81)
  - Gore, Al, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 82)
  - Gott, John, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 83)
  - Government, 1963-1985 (Box 19, Folder 84)
  - Graham, Katherine, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 85)
  - Grass - Height Restrictions, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 86)
  - Gray, Theodore, 1989-1997 (Box 19, Folder 87)
  - Great Falls - Miscellaneous, 1987-1993 (Box 19, Folder 88)
  - Great Falls - Miscellaneous 2, 1965-2002 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Great Falls and Old Dominion Railroad, 1991-1993 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Great Falls Athletic Association, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Great Falls Library, 1990-1992 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Great Falls Road, 1971-1982 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Green Spring Farm, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Greensboro LTD, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Griffin, Anthony, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Growth, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Gulledge, Charles, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Gunnell Chapel and Family, Undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Gunston Hall, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Gypsy Moth, 1987-1992 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Gypsy Moth, 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Gypsy Moth - 2001, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Hadid, Mohammed, 1989-1992 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Hager, John, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Haig, Alexander, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Halaby, Lisa/Najeeb, 1999-2003 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Hall, Carlyle, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Halpin, Gerry, 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Hand, J.M. Colton, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Handleman, Mabel and Howard, 1956-1994 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Hanes, John, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Hanley, Katherine, 1994-1996 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Hansborough, Alice, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Hansen, Gary [contains photograph], 1983 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Hanshaw, Bruce B., 1983 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Harahan, Chris, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Harn, John, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Harris, Brenda, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Harris, Jean, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Harris, Robert, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Harris, William C., 1982 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Hasan, Suraiya, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Hatch, Winslow, 1970-1980 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Hawthorne, Robert H., 1984 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Haycock Elementary, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Haycock Road, 1984-1988 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Haycock Road Associates, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Hazardous Materials, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Hazel, John T. "Til", 2000 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Hazel, William, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Hazelton Labs, 1975-1998 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Health Care, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Heastie, Earnestine, Undated (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Heckel, Dick, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Helfinstein, Bert, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Helistop, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Herrick, Carole and Philip, 1991-2001 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Herrity, John "Jack", 1975-2002 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Hertzler, Elan, Undated (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Highlander Club, Undated (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Highways, 1961-1994 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Highways, 1972-1991 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Hill, Wanda, Undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Hilton (McLean), 1990-1997 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Hilton, Howard, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Hinds, Max, 1993-1995 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Hinkle, Betsy, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Hinkle, Richard, Undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Hirst, Omer, 1975-2003 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Historical Society of Fairfax County, 1993-2004 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Historical Society of McLean, 1993-1999 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Hodgson, Alfred, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Holladay, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Holley, David, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Holley, Estelle, Undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Holly Knoll Homeowners Association, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Holmberg, Susan Lee, Undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Holton, A. Linwood and Virginia "Jinks", 1970-1999 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Holton, Dwight, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Homes, 1968-1988 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Hoofnagle, James, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Hoofnagle, William [contains photograph], 1971 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Hooking Road, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Horan, Robert F. Jr, 1975-2002 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Horton, Tom, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Horwatt, Michael, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Hospice, 1978-2000 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Housing, 1965-1983 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Howell, Janet, 1999-2002 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Hubbard, Karetta, 1977-1995 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Hubbard, Steve, 1985-1993 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Huber, Maya, 1979-1999 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Hudgins, Cathy, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Human Rights, 1975-1991 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Hunt, David M., 2002-2004 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Hunting Ridge, 1976-1996 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Iliff Nursing and Rehab Center, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Immanuel Presbyterian Church [contains photograph], 1983-1992 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Incorporation - City of McLean, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Indians, 1985-1995 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Ingleside, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Integration, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Interstate 66, 1965-1999 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Isman, Warren E., 1983 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Iverson Technology, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - J.C. Penney - Tysons Corner, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Jackson House, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Jackson, Robert H., 1996 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Jamestown 2007 Celebration, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Jaycees, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Jefferson High School for Science and Technology, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Jenkins, Walter Edward, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Jewett, Gary, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Johns, Homer, Undated (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Johnson, Walter P. (Wine Scheme), 1977-1982 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Jones, Billy, 1997-2000 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Jones, Gary, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Jones, Peter, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Jones, Thomas ap Catesby, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Jorgenson, Harold, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Judicial Center, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Junior Women’s Club of McLean, Undated (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Juvenile Court, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Kane, Michael A., 2003 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Karmol, Colleen, 1990-1996 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - Kasi, Mir Aimal, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - Kauffman, Dana, Undated (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Kay, Alan, 1983-1997 (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Keenan, Barbara, Undated (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Keller, Leeta, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Kelley, Mary Kathleen, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - Kennedy Family, 1962-2003 (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - Key Club, 1986-1989 (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Kiessling, Evelyn, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - Kilberg, Bobbie, 1989-2000 (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - King, Dr. Martin Luther, 1986-1988 (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Kinghorn, Edward J., 2003 (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - Kings Manor, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - Kirby Family, Undated (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - Kirby Road, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 78)
  - Kirby, Sheriff Eppa, Undated (Box 21, Folder 79)
  - Kirk, Alan, Undated (Box 21, Folder 80)
  - Kirkland, Lane, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 81)
  - Kissman, Katha, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 82)
  - Kiwanis Club, Undated (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - Koenig, Francis L. (and family), 1973-1999 (Box 21, Folder 84)
  - Kontzias, George, 1982-1985 (Box 21, Folder 85)
  - Koons Automotive, 1983-1988 (Box 21, Folder 86)
  - KPMG Tower, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 87)
  - Krebser, Werner, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 88)
  - Ku Klux Klan [contains photographs], 1925-1927 (Box 21, Folder 89)
  - L’Auberge Chez Francois, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 90)
  - Lake Anne, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 91)
  - Lake Fairfax Park, 1982-2001 (Box 21, Folder 92)
  - Lambert, J. Hamilton, 1978-1997 (Box 21, Folder 92)
  - Landsdowne Resort, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 93)
  - Langan, Thomas, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Langley, 1973-1994 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Langley Amoco, 1977-1991 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Langley Club, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Langley Exxon, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Langley Forest, 1974-1993 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Langley Fork, 1978-1996 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Langley Hall, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Langley High School, 1964-1997 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Langley Hill Friends, 1966-1983 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Langley Oaks, 1976-1997 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Langley Residential Support Services, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Langley School, 1961-2003 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - LaRouche, Lyndon, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Larson, Kent, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Larson, Paula, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Laughlin Realtors, 1996-2001 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Lawless, Fred, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Lebowitz, Adele, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Lechner, Ira, Undated (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Lee, Robert E., Undated (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Leesburg Pike, 1963-2003 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Lehman, Diane, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Leidinger, Bill, 1992-1996 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Leigh House, 1983-1985 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Leigh, A. Claiborne, 1959-2001 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Leiter Mansion, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Leven Preserve, 1969-1987 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Lew, Betty, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Lewinsville Civil War, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Lewinsville Park, 1971-2002 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Lewinsville Presbyterian Church, 1955-2004 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Lewinsville Road, 1985-1990 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Lewinsville School, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Lewinsville Senior Center, 1984-2003 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Lewinsville Survey [contains photographs], 1989 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Lewinsville, Town of, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Lewis, Fulton III, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Lewis, James T., 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Libertarians, Undated (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Library - McLean, 1967-1990 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Lilly, George, 1972-2000 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Lincoln at Tyson’s Corner, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Linway Terrace, 1981-1983 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Linz, Mary Grace, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Lions Club [contains photographs], 1955-1957 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Liquor, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Little League, 1982-1999 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Litton PRC, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Lodal, Elizabeth, 2000-2001 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Log Cabin - Arlington, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Lomask, Milton, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Longfellow Middle School, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Lorton Prison, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Lottery, 1987-2000 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Loudoun Events, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Lourenco, Christiane, Undated (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Loving, William H., Undated (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Lowell Avenue, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Lukens, Horace, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Luminaria, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Lupus Foundation, Undated (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Luria, Jon D., 2001 (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Lusk, Rodney L., 2002 (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Luttig, J. Michal, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Lyman, Julia, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Lynch, Edwin, 1996-1998 (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Lyon, Theodore B. "Ted", Undated (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - McAllister, Marcia, Undated (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - McConnell, Elaine, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - McCutchen, Emily, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 71)
  - McDiarmid, Dorothy, 1977-1983 (Box 22, Folder 72)
  - McDonald’s, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 73)
  - McDowell, Robert, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 74)
  - McFarland, Alvin L. [photograph included], Undated (Box 22, Folder 75)
  - McIntosh, Carl, 1990-1997 (Box 22, Folder 76)
  - McLean, 1958-2001 (Box 22, Folder 77)
  - McLean Amoco, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 78)
  - McLean Arts Club, 1988-1990 (Box 22, Folder 79)
  - McLean Bank, 1974-1985 (Box 22, Folder 80)
  - McLean Baptist Church, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 81)
  - McLean Bible Church, 1991-2000 (Box 22, Folder 82)